（走过的路）
我猜猜 你要拿自己的灵魂换吗
Let me guess, you're offering up your own soul?
你只需要复活萨姆
All you gotta do is bring Sam back.
你还有多久
How long you get?
一年
One year.
马上解除迪恩的交易
Let Dean out of his deal right now.
我也像其他人一样有老板
I got a boss like everybody.
合同在谁手里
Who holds the contract?
我不能告诉你
I can't tell you.
西方崛起了新领袖
There's a new leader rising in the West.
他不怎么喜欢你
He doesn't like you very much.
她叫莉莉丝
Her name is Lilith.
我知道你的交易 迪恩
I know about your deal, Dean.
谁告诉你的
And who told you that?
掌握合约的那个恶魔
The demon that holds it.
她也掌握了我的合约
She holds mine too.
- 她吗 - 她叫莉莉丝
- She? - Her name's Lilith.
这就是露比吗
So this is Ruby, huh?
她是个恶魔 萨姆
She's a demon, Sam.
他们想要我们死 我们想要他们死
They want us dead, we want them dead.
什么样的刀能杀恶魔
What kind of blade can kill a demon?
昨天的话 我会说没有这种东西
Yesterday, I'd have said there was no such thing.
黄眼恶魔曾经对你有大计划啊 萨姆
Yellow Eyes had some prettty big plans for you, Sam.
你很特别
That you're special.
有超感幻象的能力
In that ESP vision kind of way.
不 那已经停止了
No, that stuff's not happening anymore.
黑狗
Black Dogs.
是地狱之犬
They're seeing Hellhounds.
恶魔斗牛犬
Demonic pit bulls.
根本没办法让我不下地狱 是吧
There's no way of saving me from the pit, is there?
对
No.
我不想死
I don't wanna die.
我不想下地狱
I don't wanna go to hell.
我们会想办法救你的
We'll find a way to save you.
你死定了
You're gonna die.
这就是你将变成的模样
This is what you're gonna become.
（如今）
（地狱之犬）
查到什么有用的了吗
Dig up anything good?
没有
No,
没什么有用的
nothing good.
鲍比查到了 可算
Well, Bobby has, finally.
- 是吗 - 嗯
- Yeah? - Yeah.
他查到了找到莉莉丝的办法
A way to find Lilith.
只剩30小时了呢
And with just, uh, 30 hours to go.
我们去趟提华纳吧
Why don't we just make a TJ run, you know?
找点小妞 喝点啤酒 我们可以…
You know, some senoritas, cervezas. We could…
西语「毛驴表演」怎么说
What's Spanish for "donkey show"?
如果我们救了你
So if we do save you…
- 我们可别那么干 - 嗯
- let's never do that. - Yeah.
迪恩
Dean…
我知道现在时间很紧了
We're cutting it close, I know.
但我们能做到的
But we're gonna get this done.
我不管需要付出什么代价 迪恩
I don't care what it takes, Dean.
你不会下地狱的
You're not gonna go to hell.
我不会让你下地狱的
I'm not gonna let you.
我发誓
I swear.
一切都会没事的
Everything's gonna be okay.
嗯 好
Yeah, okay.
[邪恶力量 第3季第16集]
名字
See, a name.
便是所需要的一切
That's the whole kit and caboodle.
名字对了 仪式对了
With the right name, the right ritual,
没什么搞不定
ain't nothing you can't suss out.
比如找到莉莉丝所在的镇吗
Like the town Lilith's in?
小子 等我完事
Kid, when I get done,
我们能知道街道
we'll know the street.
印第安纳州新哈莫尼
New Harmony, Indiana.
找到了
And we have a winner.
好
All right.
我们走
Let's go.
等等 等一下的
Hold on. Holster it up there, Tex.
怎么了
What's the problem?
「怎么了」
"What's the problem"?
拜托 我从何说起
Come on. Where do I begin?
首先 我们都不知道
I mean, first of all, we don't even know.
莉莉丝是否真掌握了我的交易
if Lilith actually holds my deal.
我们是相信了贝拉的情报
We're going off of Bela's intel.
那贱人吐气时 吐出来的都是浑气
And when that bitch breathes, the air comes out crooked, okay?
其次 即便我们能找到莉莉丝
Second, even if we could get to Lilith,
我们也没办法杀她
we have no way to gank her.
第三 这个莉莉丝
And third, isn't this the same Lilith.
不是还想把你的大脑袋插在棍子上吗
that wants your giant head on a pike?
还要我继续说吗
Should I continue?
你还真会搞气氛
Ain't you just bringing down the room?
是啊 天赋
Yeah. Well, it's a gift.
抱歉 那我们要怎么办 迪恩
I'm sorry, so then, what are we supposed to do, Dean?
虽然我要死了 不代表你也要死
Just cause I gotta die. Doesn't mean you have to. Okay.
我们如果不能有计划地去 就别去
Either, we go in smart or we don't go in at all.
好啊 如果是这样 那我有办法
Okay. Fine. If that's the case, I have the answer.
- 是吗 - 嗯
- You do? - Yeah,
绝对能证实那就是莉莉丝
a sure-fire way to confirm it's Lilith.
还能让我们拿到货真价实能杀恶魔的东西
And a way to get us a bona fide, demon-killing Ginsu.
该死 萨姆 不行
Damn it, Sam, no.
我们没得可争了
We are so past arguing.
迪恩 我要召唤露比
Dean, I am summoning Ruby.
你休想 我们的麻烦够多了
The hell you are, we've enough problems as it is.
就是
Exactly.
我们没时间 没选择了
And we got no time and no choice either.
得了 她是撒谎贱人的环球小姐 好吗
Come on, man, she is the Miss Universe of lying skanks, okay?
她跟你说她能救我
She told you that she could save me?
撒谎
Lie.
她似乎对莉莉丝无所不知
She seems to know everything about Lilith…
但偏巧忘记说 哎呦
but forgot to mention, right,
莉莉丝掌握着我的灵魂
Lilith owns my soul.
好吧 行 她是个撒谎精
Okay, fine, she's a liar.
但她还是有那把刀
She's still got that knife.
- 迪恩 - 说不定她就是莉莉丝的手下
- Dean… - For all we know, she works for Lilith.
那再给我个别的选择 迪恩
Then, give me another option, Dean,
告诉我还能怎么办
I mean, tell me what else.
- 萨姆是对的 - 不 该死
- Sam's right. - No, damn it.
不行
Just no.
我们不能再犯同样错误了
We are not gonna make the same mistakes all over again.
你们想救我 另想办法
You guys wanna save me? Find something else.
你去哪 鲍比
Where're you going, Bobby?
看来是要去
I guess to.
另想办法
find something else.
电话也能用的
You know, phones work too.
萨姆
Sam.
怎么样啊
How's tricks?
你怎么能移动得那么快
How do you get around so fast?
我有超级碗杯喷气背包
I got the Super Bowl jetpack.
那么
So…
你找我
you called?
你知道吗
Did you know?
你得再给点信息
Gonna need a tiny bit more.
迪恩的交易
About Dean's deal.
莉莉丝握着他的合同
That Lilith holds the contract.
我知道
Yes, I did.
怎么 你就没觉得那很重要吗
And what? You didn't think that was important?
- 你们没准备好 - 什么意思
- You weren't ready. - For what?
如果我早说了
If I told you,
你俩蠢蛋会准备不充分地去找她
you two yahoos would have just charged after her halfcocked.
莉莉丝就会把你们漂亮脸蛋上的肉
And Lilith would have peeled the meat.
一点点撕下来
from your pretty, pretty faces.
我们现在准备好了
Well, we're ready now.
我要你的刀
I want your knife.
你说对了一件事
You're right about one thing.
如果你真准备好了
If you are ready…
那现在时机也正好
And now's the time too.
莉莉丝正好没防备
Lilith's guard's down.
是吗
Is that so?
她在度假
She's on shore leave.
休息放松
A little R and R.
那什么意思
What the hell does that mean?
相信我 你不想知道
Trust me, you don't wanna know.
你们没弄丢我给你的巫术袋吧
You didn't lose those hex bags I gave you?
还在
We got them.
很好 那她就不会觉察到你们靠近了
Good, then she won't sense that you're coming.
你会把刀给我们吗
So you'll give us the knife?
不会
No.
但你刚说…
But you just said…
你想拿把杀猪刀就冲进去吗
You wanna charge in with one little pig-sticker?
那是浪费大好时机
It's a waste of a true-blue window.
就像拿公文箱炸弹刺杀希特勒
Like hitting Hitler with that exploding briefcase.
- 别想了 - 好吧 那怎么办
- Forget it. - Okay, then how?
我知道怎么救你哥哥 萨姆
I know how to save your brother, Sam.
不 你不知道
No, you don't.
你对迪恩说了你做不到 你一直在对我撒谎
You told Dean you couldn't. You've been lying to me all along.
所以把你的刀给我吧
So just give me your damn knife.
我没有对你撒谎
You're not the one that I've been lying to.
- 那你能救他吗 - 不能
- So you can save him? - No.
但你能
But you can.
什么
What?
萨姆
Sam,
你有上帝赐予的能力
you've got some God-given talent.
好吧 不是上帝赐予的 但你懂的
Well, not God-given, but you get the gist.
灵力吗
All that psychic crap?
黄眼死后就没了
That's gone ever since Yellow Eyes died.
不是没了
Not gone.
只是休眠了
Dormant.
而且不光是幻象
And not just visions either.
你以为莉莉丝为什么那么怕你
Why do you think Lilith is so scared of you?
好啊 她怕我
Right, she's scared of me.
如果你想
If you wanted,
你不动一块肌肉就能灭了她
you could wipe her off the map without moving a muscle.
我不相信你
I don't believe you.
是真的
It's the truth.
你决定现在才跟我说吗
And you decided to tell me this just now?
恶魔
Demon?
操纵人心算是本职工作
Manipulative's kind of in the job description.
事实就是 你绝不会考虑的
Fact is, is that you never would have considered it.
- 除非你… - 足够绝望吗
- Not until you were… - Desperate enough?
你不喜欢与众不同
You don't like being different.
你讨厌迪恩有时看你的眼光
You hate the way Dean looks at you sometimes.
就好像你是个马戏团怪胎
Like you're some sort of sideshow freak.
但忍着吧
But suck it up,
因为我们要说得还很多
because we got a lot of ground to cover.
而且我们得尽快开始 但我们能做到
and we gotta do it fast, but we can do it.
说我是贱人 随你怎么恨我
Look, call me a bitch, hate me all you want,
但我从未对你撒过谎 萨姆
but I have never lied to you, Sam.
从未
Not ever.
我告诉你
And I'm telling you,
你可以救你哥哥
you can save your brother.
我可以教你怎么做
And I can show you how.
你是这样的人啊
So that's you, huh?
我们的荡妇尤达大师
Our slutty little Yoda.
迪恩
Dean.
还是那么讨人喜欢
Charming as ever.
我就知道你会来
I knew you'd show up.
因为我知道萨姆不会听我话
Because I knew Sam wouldn't listen.
但你别想教他什么
But you're not gonna teach him anything.
听到了吗 除非我死了
You understand me? Over my dead body.
这你说对了
Well, you're right about that.
但你要把那把刀给我
What you are gonna do is give me that knife.
然后你要爬回你来的那个深渊里
And then you just go crawl back into whatever slop you came from,
永远别再来打扰我和我弟弟了 明白了吗
and never bother me and my brother again, are we clear?
你弟弟体内有个炸弹
Your brother is carrying a bomb inside of him,
我们不用它就太蠢了
and we'd be stupid not to use it.
- 迪恩 等一下 - 萨姆 别
- Dean, look, just hold on… - Sam, don't.
拜托 你瞎了吗
Come on, man, what are you blind?
你看不出这是诡计吗
Can't you see that this is a trick?
不是的
That's not true.
她希望你屈服于
She wants you to give in.
这恶魔灵力什么的
to this whole demonic, psychic whatever, okay?
她可能希望你做她的
I mean, hell, she probably wants you to become her little.
反基督超级明星
Antichrist superstar.
我想要莉莉丝死
I want Lilith dead.
仅此而已
That's all.
为什么
Why?
我告诉你了
I've told you why.
对哦 因为你曾是人类
Right, yeah. Because you were human once.
你喜欢猫咪和在海滩上漫步
And you like kittens and long walks on the beach.
我受够了向你证明自己
You know, I am so sick of proving myself to you.
你想自救吗
You wanna save yourself?
这就是唯一办法 你个没骨气的蠢混蛋
This is how, you dumb, spineless dick.
露比
Ruby.
你笑什么
What the hell are you grinning at?
少了什么东西吗
Missing something?
我宰了你 你个混蛋
I'll kill you, you son of a bitch.
我说了
Like I said,
我就知道你会来
I knew you'd come.
等等
Wait,
你就把我丢在这里吗
you're just gonna leave me here?
走吧 萨姆
Let's go, Sam.
你就是蠢到不想活了吗
So you're just too stupid to live, is that it?
好啊
Then fine.
你活该下地狱
You deserve hell.
我真希望我也在那里 迪恩
And I wish I could be there, Dean.
我希望我能闻到你骨头上的肉被烫掉
I wish I could smell the flesh sizzle off your bones.
我希望我能在那里听到你的尖叫
I wish I could be there to hear you scream!
我还希望你闭嘴呢
And I wish you'd shut your pie hole,
但我们不是总能得偿所愿
but we don't always get what we want.
我们就让露比在下面发霉吗
We're just gonna let Ruby rot down there?
是这意思
That's the idea.
迪恩 如果…
Dean, what if…?
如果露比是对的呢
What if Ruby's right?
如果我能干掉莉莉丝呢
What if I can take out Lilith?
别那么看着我
Quit looking at me like that.
怎么 你要魔女嘉莉瞪她
What? You gonna give her the Carrie stare.
莉莉丝就炸了吗
and Lilith goes poof?
我不知道露比什么意思
I don't know what Ruby meant.
或许我们该去问问她
You know, maybe we should just go ask her.
萨姆 你想要刀 我帮你拿到了
Sam, you wanted the knife, I got you the knife.
迪恩 听我说一句
Dean, just listen to me for a second.
上次 莉莉丝弹个指响
Last time, Lilith snapped her fingers.
就让30个恶魔来围堵我们
and put 30 demons on our ass.
我们就一把小刀吗
And all we got is one little knife?
就像你说的 我们如果没个好计划就不该去
I mean, like you said, we go in smart or we don't go in at all.
是啊 这不够好
Yeah. Well, this ain't smart.
我们只有一个机会 迪恩
We got one shot at this, Dean. Just one.
如果有什么万无一失的办法
So if there's a sure-fire way,
那或许我们该考虑一下
then maybe we should just talk about it.
萨姆 我们不能再犯同样的错误了
Sam, we are not gonna make the same mistake all over again.
这话你说过了 但那什么意思
You said that, but what does that even mean?
你还看不出规律吗
Don't you see a pattern here?
爸爸的交易 我的 现在又是这个
Dad's deal, my deal, now this.
每次我们中有一人陷入困境
I mean, every time one of us is up the creek,
另一个就迫不及待地出卖灵魂
the other's begging to sell their soul.
就是这样
That's all this is, man.
露比是在把你往邪路上带
Ruby's just jerking your chain down the road.
你清楚那是什么路 你清楚那通往何方
You know what it's paved with, and you know where it's going.
迪恩
Dean.
你怕会发生什么
What are you afraid is gonna happen?
是我啊 我能应付
This is me, I can handle it.
如果能救你
And if it'll save you…
何必冒险
Why even risk it?
因为你是我哥哥
Because you're my brother.
因为你也为我做了这样的事
Because you did the same thing for me.
是啊
I know.
看看结果如何
And look how that turned out.
我就是说
All I'm saying…
萨姆 我就是说你是我的弱点
Sammy, all I'm saying is that you're my weak spot.
是的
You are.
我也是你的
And I'm yours.
不 你不是真心的
No, you don't mean that. We're…
我们是家人
We're family.
我知道
I know.
那些坏蛋也知道
And those evil sons of bitches know it too.
我们愿为彼此做的事 愿做到什么程度
I mean, what we'll do for each other, you know, how far we'll go.
他们在以此对付我们
They're using it against us.
那我们就不再照顾彼此了吗
So what we just stop looking out for each other?
不 我们不再牺牲自己了
No, we stop being martyrs.
我们不再替这些恶魔省事了
Man, we stop spreading it for these demons.
我们拿上刀
We take this knife.
以我们的方式去对付莉莉丝
and we go after Lilith our way.
爸爸教我们的方式
The way Dad taught us to.
如果我们要死
And if we go down, then…
也要英勇就义
then we go down swinging.
你觉得呢
What do you think?
我觉得你刚刚绝对该配上
I think you totally should have been jamming.
《老虎之眼》做背乐
"Eye of the Tiger" right there.
咬我吧
Bite me.
这段话我练过了
You know, I totally rehearsed that speech too.
印第安纳州
So, Indiana?
是啊 莉莉丝在度假
Yeah, where Lilith is on shore leave.
是吧
Yeah, I guess.
告诉我
Tell me something.
恶魔会做什么消遣
What the hell does a demon do for fun?
（印第安纳州 新哈莫尼）
（弗里芒家）
- 帕特 - 汤姆
- Pat. - Tom.
你孙女怎么样了
How's that granddaughter of yours?
患病在家呢 小可怜
Home sick, poor thing.
就近来到处传染的那病
Darn bug that's going around now.
太可惜了
That's too bad.
那你要替我和朱蒂好好抱抱她
Well, you give her a big old hug from me and Judy.
没问题
You bet, man.
悠着点 汤姆
Take her easy, Tom.
你也是 帕特
You too, Pat.
（帮帮我们）
她在哪
Where is she?
楼上 跟雀斑玩呢
Upstairs, playing with Freckles.
如果我们只坐在这里
If we just sit here,
就死定了
we're dead.
她会听到的
She'll hear you.
不是她死就是我们亡
It's her or us.
那可是我的女儿
It's my baby girl.
现在不是了
Not anymore.
她体内有什么别的东西
There's something inside her.
闭上嘴
Shut your mouth.
她来了
She's coming.
你们刚刚说什么呢
What were you guys talking about?
就是我们多爱你
Just how much we love you.
你的裙子怎么了
What happened to your dress?
雀斑对我好凶
Freckles was mean to me.
那…
That's…
那好啊 亲爱的
That's nice, dear.
爸爸 你可以推我荡秋千吗
Daddy, will you push me on the swing?
当然 亲爱的
Well, sure, honey.
但你不想先换衣服吗
But don't you wanna change first?
你可不希望邻居看到
I mean, you don't want the neighbors to see.
那么多血
all that blood.
你好聪明 我爱你爸爸
You're so smart. I love you, Daddy.
我也爱你
I love you too.
亲爱的
Sweetie,
等过一阵的
you think maybe after a while…
你能不能…
do you think maybe you could…
放了我们
let us go?
为什么
Why?
我…
I…
我不知道
Well, I don't know.
你不想待在这里吗
Don't you wanna be here?
你不爱我吗
Don't you love me?
我当然爱你
Well, sure, I do.
我们都爱你 亲爱的
We all do, honey.
我们都好爱你
We all love you so much.
别对我不好 爸爸
Don't be mean to me, Daddy.
就像雀斑 还有那个叫啥的老婆子保姆
Like Freckles or what's-her-name, that mean old babysitter.
对不起
I… I'm sorry.
没事 傻瓜 我们去玩吧
That's okay, silly. Now let's go and play.
你们想去哪
Where do you think you're going?
我们拿到刀了
We got the knife.
你们打算不带我去吗
And you intend to use it without me.
你看我像个能丢下的舞会舞伴吗
Do I look like a ditch-able prom date to you?
不 鲍比 当然不是
No, Bobby, of course not.
这是我和萨姆的事
This is about me and Sam.
这不是你的战斗
Okay, this isn't your fight.
怎么不是
The hell it isn't.
家人不限于血脉 小子
Family don't end with blood, boy.
再说 你们需要我
Besides, you need me.
- 鲍比 - 你在带伤上阵
- Bobby… - You're playing wounded.
告诉我 你出现多少幻觉了
Tell me, how many hallucinations have you had so far?
你怎么知道
How'd you know?
因为 你被地狱之犬追杀时就会这样
Because, that's what happens when you got Hellhounds on your butt.
而且因为我聪明
And because I'm smart.
我跟着你们
I'll follow.
别每10分钟就停车撒尿
Don't be stopping to pee every 10 minutes either.
迪恩
Dean?
嗯
Yeah?
如果这事…
You know, if this doesn't…
如果这事不能如我们所愿 我要你知道
If this doesn't go the way we want, I want you to know…
不不不
No, no, no, no, no, no.
不什么
"No" what?
你别眼泪汪汪地跟我道别 好吗
You're not gonna bust out the misty goodbye speech, okay?
如果这是我在世间的最后一天了
And if this is my last day on earth,
我可不想搞得气氛尴尬
I do not want it to be socially awkward.
你知道我想要什么吗
You know what I do want?
- 邦乔维 - 邦乔维偶尔也不错
- Bon Jovi? - Bon Jovi rocks on occasion.
*我走过这些街道*
*And I walk these streets, *
*背后背着吉他*
*A loaded six-string on my back*
*我不闹着玩*
*I play for keeps, *
来啊
Come on.
*因为我可能有去无回*
*'cause I might not make it back*
*我走遍了各处*
*I've been everywhere, *
- *耶* - *我站得直*
- *Yeah.* - *And I'm standing tall*
*我见过无数面庞*
*I've seen a million faces*
*我震撼了他们所有人*
*and I've rocked them all*
*因为我是个牛仔*
*'Cause I'm a cowboy, *
*我骑在钢马上*
*On a steel horse I ride*
- *我被通缉* - *被通缉*
- *I'm wanted* - *Wanted*
*不论死活*
*Dead or alive*
我们要被叫停了
We're getting pulled over?
我尾灯坏了一个
I got a busted taillight.
反正我们又不急
It's not like we're in a hurry or nothing.
有事吗 警官
Problem, officer?
请出示驾照和行驶证
License and registration, please.
你知道你坏了个尾灯吗 海嘉先生
Do you realize you have a taillight out, Mr. Hagar?
是的
Yes.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
我一直想着要修一下呢
You know, I've been meaning to take care of that.
事实上
As a matter of fact…
迪恩
Dean.
怎么回事啊
What the hell happened?
迪恩刚杀了个恶魔
Dean just killed a demon.
你怎么知道的
How'd you know?
我就是知道
I just knew.
我能看到它的脸
I could see its face.
那张脸下的真脸
Its real face under that one.
怎么 你现在能看到恶魔了
So, what? Now you're seeing demons?
我近来看到了各种东西 但是
I've been seeing all kinds of things lately, but.
这个是新的
nothing like this.
其实 这并不疯狂
Actually, it's not all that crazy.
这怎么不疯狂了
How's it not that crazy?
你还剩多久 五个多小时了吗
What you got? Just over five hours to go?
你要穿过阴阳隔界了 迪恩
You're piercing the veil, Dean.
你能瞥见B面了
You're glimpsing the B-side.
别那么新时代好吗
Little less New Age-y, please.
你快成地狱贱民了
You're almost hell's bitch.
所以你能看到其他地狱贱民
So you can see hell's other bitches.
谢谢了
Thank you.
这还挺方便的
Well, it'll actually come in pretty handy.
很高兴我被诅咒的灵魂还能派上用场
Well, I'm glad my doomed soul's good for something.
说对了
Damn right it is.
莉莉丝可能在镇上到处安了恶魔
Lilith's probably got demons stashed all over town.
我们不能让他们奏响警报
We can't let them sound the alarm.
如果她知道我们来了
If she knows we're here,
我们肯定出师未捷身先死
we're dead before we started.
这计划太棒了
Well, this is a terrific plan.
我很激动能参与其中 我们可以走了吗
I'm excited to be a part of it. Can we go, please?
生日快乐 亲爱的
Happy birthday, sweetie.
- 生日快乐 - 生日快乐
- Happy birthday. - Happy birthday.
太好了 每天都是我生日
Yay, it's my birthday every day.
蛋糕
Cake.
又吃
Again.
太好了
It's good.
爷爷 能问你件事吗
Grandpa, can I ask you something?
当然 小糖豆 随便问
Sure, jellybean, anything.
你为什么企图向维普林先生求助
Why'd you try to go to Mr. Weprin for help?
我没有
Well, I didn't.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you mean.
你个大骗子
You're a big fat liar.
对不起
I'm sorry.
那是个错误
It was a mistake.
你俩知道吗
Did you two know about this?
不知道
No.
爷爷
Grandpa,
- 你不爱我吗 - 我爱你
- you don't love me? - I do.
我爱你的
I do. I love you.
不 你不爱我
No, you don't.
你又在撒谎了
You're lying again.
你就是坏老头
You're just a mean old man.
做点什么
Do something.
救救我
Help me, please.
我觉得我不喜欢你了
I don't think I like you anymore.
谁都不许叫
Nobody scream, okay?
尖叫让我生气
Screaming makes me mad.
妈妈 我可以再吃点冰淇淋吗
Mommy, can I have ice cream with mine?
（待售）
是那个小女孩
It's the little girl.
天啊 她的脸好丑
God, her face is awful.
好 那我们走吧 我们在浪费时间
All right, then let's go. We're wasting time.
等等
Wait.
等什么
For what?
等她把剩下的人都杀了吗
For her to kill the rest of them?
嗯 如果我们不小心也要送命
Yeah, and us too, if we're not careful.
看
Look.
看到那个晚上9点还在工作的邮递员了吗
See the real go-getter mailman on the clock at 9 p.m?
还有那边的罗杰斯先生
And Mr. Rogers over there.
恶魔吗
Demons?
对
Yes.
好吧 那我们干掉那些人 再偷溜进去
Okay, fine. We… We ninja past those guys, sneak in.
然后呢 把一个10岁小姑娘割喉吗
Then what, give a Colombian necktie to a ten-year-old girl?
- 得了 - 迪恩
- Come on. - Look, Dean,
- 我知道这很糟 - 还用你说
- I know it's awful. - You think?
这不光是救你 迪恩
This isn't just about saving you, Dean.
这是救所有人
This is about saving everybody.
她必须被阻止 孩子
She's gotta be stopped, son.
该死
Damn it.
再读一遍 妈妈
Read it again, Mommy.
但我都读26次了
But I've read it 26 times.
再读一次
Again.
「很久很久以前
"Once upon a time,
在塞勒涅镇
in the town of Selene…
住了个美丽的公主 柯丽奥
lived a beautiful princess named Cleo.
但小镇当时被一只恶龙侵扰
But the town was plagued with an evil dragon…
它要求血祭儿童
that demanded the blood of the children.
公主注定要被祭祀给
And the princess was doomed to be sacrificed.
那黑暗可怕的恶龙「
to the dark and terrible dragon."
请把我的刀还我
I'd like my knife back, please.
否则拧断你的脖子
Or your neck snaps like a chicken bone.
刀不在他那里
He doesn't have it.
别激动
Take it easy.
你怎么出来的
How the hell did you get out?
你不知道我的事能写本书了
What you don't know about me could fill a book.
怎么了
What?
没事
Nothing. I just…
我以前看不到 但你真丑爆了
I couldn't see it before, but you are one ugly broad.
萨姆
Sam,
把刀给我 别伤到你自己了
give me the knife before you hurt yourself.
等一切结束再给你
You'll get it when this is over.
已经结束了
It's already over.
我给了你救迪恩的办法 你拒绝了
I gave you a way to save Dean, you shot me down.
现在太迟了
Now it's too late.
他死定了
He's dead.
我不会让你也一起死
And I'm not gonna let you die too.
你敢阻止我
Try and stop me.
我就杀了你
and I'll kill you,
- 贱人 - 放马过来吧 亲爱的
- bitch. - Hit me with your best shot, baby.
两位
Guys, guys.
稍后再吵吧
Have your little catfight later.
- 看来别想偷袭了 - 快走
- So much for the element of surprise. - Go. Go.
跑啊
Run, run.
好吧
Okay, okay.
鲍比在干什么呢
What the hell's taking Bobby?
我在开了
I'm trying.
你觉得莉莉丝知道我们来了吗
You think Lilith knows we're here?
可能吧
Probably.
我们是来帮忙的 好吗
We're here to help, okay?
我这就把手放开
I'm gonna move my hand,
我们小声说话 好吗
and we're gonna talk nice and quiet. Okay?
先生 你女儿呢
Sir, where is your daughter?
那不…
It's not…
那不是她了
It's not her anymore.
她在哪
Where is she?
在楼上
Upstairs.
在她卧室里
In her bedroom.
好吧 听我说
Okay, okay. Listen to me.
我要你下楼 去地下室
I want you to go downstairs to the basement,
关上门 撒一道盐
put a line of salt at the door behind you.
明白了吗
Do you understand me?
我得带上我妻子
Not without my wife.
- 等不起了 - 不行
- Yes, without your wife. - No.
动手吧
Do it.
快啊
Hurry!
不是她
It's not her.
不在女孩身体里了
It's not in the girl anymore.
妈妈
Mommy.
妈妈在呢
Mommy's here.
妈妈在呢 没事了
Mommy's here. It's okay.
该死
Damn it.
好吧 不管你听到什么
All right. No matter what you hear,
你和你丈夫 女儿都要待在地下室里
you and your husband and your daughter stay in the basement.
好
Okay.
我也不想说早告诉你了
Well, I hate to be a told-you-so.
好吧 露比 她在哪
All right, Ruby, where is she?
我不知道
I don't know.
她能突破洒水器吗
Well, can she get past the sprinklers?
她这种级别的 才不在乎圣水呢
At her pay grade, she ain't sweating the holy water.
好吧 你赢了 我需要做什么
Okay, you win. What do I have to do?
- 什么意思 - 救迪恩
- What do you mean? - To save Dean.
你需要我做什么
What do you need me to do?
你在干什么
What the hell do you think you're doing?
先别说话
Just shut up for a second.
- 露比 - 我给过你机会
- Ruby. - You had your chance.
那不是打开个开关那么简单
You can't just flip a switch.
我们需要时间的
We needed time.
肯定还有办法 肯定有什么
Well, there's gotta be something, there's gotta be some way.
不管什么我都做
Whatever it is, I'll do it.
别 迪恩 我不能允许你下地狱
Don't, Dean. I'm not gonna let you go to hell.
- 迪恩 - 你没别的办法
- Dean. - Yes, you are!
只能这样
Yes, you are.
对不起
I'm sorry.
这都怪我
I mean, this was all my fault.
我知道
I know that.
但你这么做 也救不了我
But what you're doing is not gonna save me.
只会害死你
It's only gonna kill you.
那我要怎么办
Then what am I supposed to do?
坚持斗争
Keep fighting.
照顾好我的车
Take care of my wheels.
萨姆 记住爸爸教你的
Sam, remember what Dad taught you.
好吗
Okay?
记住我教你的
And remember what I taught you.
很遗憾 迪恩
I'm sorry, Dean.
我都不会希望我最恨的敌人遭受这个
I wouldn't wish this upon my worst enemy.
地狱之犬
Hellhound.
在哪
Where?
那里
There.
给我刀 或许我能打过它
Give me the knife. Maybe I can fight it off.
- 什么 - 快点
- What? - Come on.
那巫尘撑不了多久
That dust won't last forever.
等等
Wait.
你想死吗
You wanna die?
萨姆 那不是露比
Sam, that's not Ruby.
那不是露比
It's not Ruby.
你在她体内多久了
How long have you been in her?
没多久
Not long.
但我喜欢
But I like it.
好成年 好漂亮
It's all grown-up and pretty.
露比呢
And where's Ruby?
她很不乖
She was a very bad girl.
所以我把她赶跑了
So I sent her far, far away.
我早该看出来的
You know, I should've seen it before.
但你们在我看来都一样
But you all look alike to me.
你好 萨姆
Hello, Sam.
我早就想见你了
I've wanted to meet you for a very long time.
你的嘴唇好软
Your lips are soft.
好吧 你抓到我了
All right, so you have me.
放了我哥哥
Let my brother go.
傻瓜
Silly goose.
你想讨价还价 你得有我想要的东西
You want a bargain, you have to have something that I want.
你没有
You don't.
这就是你的大计划吗
So is this your big plan, huh?
把我拖下地狱
Drag me to hell,
杀了萨姆
kill Sam,
然后呢
and then what?
成为贱人女王吗
Become queen bitch?
我不需要回答狗食
I don't have to answer to puppy chow.
咬死他 小子们
Sic him, boy.
不
No!
不 停下
No, stop.
停下
Stop.
Stop it!
不
No.
停下
Stop it.
Stop it!
不
No.
太好了
Yes.
退后
Back.
我说 退后
I said, back.
去死吧
I don't think so.
不
No.
迪恩
Dean.
不
No!
No.
不
谁救救我
Somebody help me.
萨姆
Sam!